Is it still hot?
هل ما زالت ساخنة؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
I shouldn't be in the State Preceptor's Mansion.
لا ينبغي أن أكون في قصر رئيس الدولة.
This is an order from the State Preceptor.
هذا أمر من رئيس الدولة.
We were like that last night.
كنا هكذا الليلة الماضية.
What happened to you and me?
ماذا حدث لي ولكم؟
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
You,
أنت،
Me,
أنا،
Don't you remember?
الا تتذكر؟
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
State Preceptor will not be responsible for it.
لن يكون مدير الدولة مسؤولاً عن ذلك.
Don't you think so?
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
Fusu,
ملاكمة،
I'm really sorry, State Preceptor.
أنا آسف حقًا ، مدير الدولة.
Adult mermen go crazy every full moon night.
حورية البحر البالغة تصاب بالجنون كل ليلة اكتمال القمر.
So I really don't remember
لذلك أنا حقا لا أتذكر
what happened last night?
ماذا حدث الليلة الماضية
If I do anything out of line,
إذا فعلت أي شيء خارج الخط ،
please punish me, State Preceptor.
من فضلك عاقبني ، مدير الدولة.
A full moon night is abnormal,
ليلة اكتمال القمر غير طبيعية ،
you are a merman not a werewolf,
أنت حوري البحر ولست بالذئب ،
You think I'm so gullible,
تعتقد أنني ساذج للغاية ،
but State Preceptor doesn't believe me anyway.
لكن معلم الدولة لا يصدقني على أي حال.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
Stop!
قف!
I was very satisfied with your performance last night.
لقد كنت راضيًا جدًا عن أدائك الليلة الماضية.
Then.
ثم.
Your Excellency is willing to take responsibility for me.
سعادتكم على استعداد لتحمل المسؤولية عني.
Let me think about it.
دعني افكر به.
Are you going to kick me out?
هل ستطردني؟
Stay here for now.
ابق هنا الآن.
Mermen
حورية البحر
are in estrus at the age of 18.
كانت في حالة شبق في سن 18.
Every night when the moon is full, the strength is weak
كل ليلة عندما يكتمل القمر تكون القوة ضعيفة
and the Qi is weak. Once combined,
و Qi ضعيف.  بمجرد الجمع ،
You only recognize one person in your life.
أنت تتعرف على شخص واحد فقط في حياتك.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Is it good?
هل هذا جيد؟
Delicious.
لذيذ.
Sit down and eat together.
اجلس وتناول الطعام معًا.
My mother loved your human food,
أحببت والدتي طعامك البشري ،
when she was little,
عندما كانت صغيرة،
She often makes me cold cakes,
غالبًا ما تصنع لي كعكات باردة ،
but why don't you eat them?
لكن لماذا لا تأكلهم؟
After my mother disappeared,
بعد أن اختفت والدتي ،
I never ate it again.
لم اقم بتناولها مرة اخرى
Even if some people haven't seen the memories and good tastes
حتى لو لم ير بعض الناس الذكريات والأذواق الطيبة
they left us for a long time.
تركونا لفترة طويلة.
It will make us reminisce for the rest of our lives.
سيجعلنا نتذكر بقية حياتنا.
She left so early,
لقد غادرت مبكرا جدا ،
I can hardly remember what she looked like.
لا أستطيع أن أتذكر كيف كانت تبدو.
I remember
أتذكر
your mother's name is Yanchu, right?
اسم والدتك هو يانشو ، أليس كذلك؟
Your Excellency, have you met my mother?
سعادتكم هل قابلت والدتي؟